fuskator.com 2018-10-11

# Privacy Policy

Last modified: January 28, 2014

This Privacy Policy applies to all pages and subdomains of "fuskator.com". By using our services and/or registering with Fuskator, you acknowledge and accept the provisions in this Privacy Policy and grant us permission to collect, store, and use the items of personal information described herein, so long as Fuskator adheres to the standards set forth more clearly below. 

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and provide such amendments to you by posting a revised version on our website. If the revised version includes a substantial change, we will provide you with thirty (30) days’ notice prior to the effectiveness thereof by posting notice of the change in a prominent place on the Fuskator website, such as presenting to you a click-through page immediately following your account login. Otherwise, in the case of insubstantial changes, the revised version will be effective at the time we post it. In any event, we will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most changes will be minor. 

If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy please contact us. 

## Information we collect

We may collect the following types of information: 

### Information you give us

When you register for a username, we ask you for personal information (such as your email address, username, and an account password). In order to improve the quality of our services and to provide you with a better user experience, we may combine the information you submit with information provided by third parties. 

### Demographic Information

Each time you access our website, our servers may automatically collect and store certain information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website. This may include your IP address, the date and time of your request, browser type, browser language, and one or more cookies (see description below) that may uniquely identify your browser. Aggregate, non-individual membership demographic information may be shared with third parties with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship who may offer products or services we believe you may be interested in. 

### Tracking Links

We may present links that include codes that enable us to track whether these links have been followed. This information is used to improve the quality of our advertising and customized content, as well as the organization and layout of our website. 

### Cookies

Assuming your browser is configured to accept them, when you visit our websites, we will send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your browser. We may also set one or more cookies in your browser when you click on an ads or other links presented on our website. Cookies make it possible to store user preferences and record which portions of our website you and other users are using the most. We use cookies for the purposes of preventing fraud and improving the quality of our website. 

### Local storage

We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches. 

### Anonymous identifiers

We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit our website, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your browser. 

## Use of Personal Information

We process personal information only for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. In addition to the reasons set forth above, such purposes also include: 

  * Providing our services which includes displaying customized advertising and other content
  * Marketing and sales of advertising
  * Auditing, research, and analysis to maintain, protect, and improve our services
  * Technical diagnostics to ensure our network is functioning as expected
  * Protecting the rights or property of third parties (e.g. copyright holders)
  * To comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system

We process personal information on our servers, which are located in Netherlands and France. As a result, there exists the possibility that we may process your personal information on a server that is not located in your home country. In some cases, we may process personal information at the request of third parties and according to their instructions, such as our advertising partners. We will treat all personal information processed at the request of a third party exactly as if we had collected the processed personal information ourselves. 

## Information we share

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of Fuskator unless one of the following circumstances applies: 

### With your consent

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Fuskator when we have your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 

### For external processing

We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

### For legal reasons

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Fuskator if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: 

  * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
  * enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
  * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
  * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Fuskator, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

### Information security

We restrict access to personal information to Fuskator employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations. 

If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy please contact us.
